[ED]
[FAST FORWARD]
Here we go!
Equal Love 6th Anniversary YouTube Live!
Yay!
Yes, that's right!
Today, September 6, is Equal Love's 6th birthday!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday everyone!
Many comments from fans!
Thank you very much!
Now once again, I think 6 years is a long time,
How do you like it, Chiara? How do you feel about it?
You've got to be kidding me! From the beginning.
How about you, Kiara, the three sisters from the beginning?
Yes, I do.
Yes. Hey, today, junior high school students,
What tool did you get? It was a tool like that,
What tool is this?
What tool did you get?
It's kind of painful.
It was like I was a member of society,
That's very thoughtful.
Yes, it is.
It's very thoughtful.
It's very beautiful, just like the script.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you. Let's hear one more.
How about you, Sana?
Well, I'm a college student myself,
I'm a university student, so I'm doing it freshly.
I'm doing it freshly.
I'm doing it.
Did you do it?
Are you doing it?Are you doing it?
I don't know.
I don't know. So, such a long history,
I had them do it cheerfully.
Thank you very much.
Such a long history,
We are celebrating the 6th anniversary of Equal Love,
Today, we have prepared a special 6th anniversary-like event,
I would like to enjoy this event with all the fans.
I look forward to working with you all until the end.
Now then, let's move on to the first project.
Just like last year, Hana drew the project flip for us.
Thank you very much.
Now let's go to the first one.
Let's see.
Six years of Equal Love & Sixth year review talk.
Yay.
Mela mela mela.
This one is based on the results of the preliminary questionnaire answered by everyone,
This is a project to look back and talk about the 6 years or the first year of the 6th year.
So let's get started.
Here is the first topic.
The cutest pictures of the members taken in the 6th year.
Yay.
So, first of all, as a look back at the 6th year, we are looking for the cutest pictures of Ikolab-chan taken by our members this year.
So let's get started. First of all, here is Maika's photo. Here you go.
Ha-ha-ha.
My first character Isai-chan.
Behind her, me.
Shadow, I look like a shadow.
I'm the one with the reflective ball.
Everyone is so cute. Of the blue Crocs.
Yes, they are. I knew Chiara and Hitomi were cute.
I'm not cute, am I?I'm not pretty, am I?
You are cute.
It was raining, so we were all wearing hats, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
But I didn't take this picture.
This is me.
Huh?
It wasn't me.
I thought it was me.
Well, I got it from my manager.
Ha-ha-ha.
That sounds like Kiran.
We all want to shoot together.
That's right.
I guess you thought everyone was sleeping like me.
I was sleeping.
But there's no one here.
I wonder which side they were on.
I'm sure.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I was sleeping.
I was sleeping.
I see.
You let me sleep.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's a lot of pictures with a lot of writing.
Thank you.
It's so cute. I love this.
It's a nice picture.
Well, well, well, I'd like to continue.
Let's keep going.
Next is a picture Iori sent me.
Here you go.Go ahead.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I wish you could have shown me this one at a time.
Ha-ha-ha.
It was a close call.
Yes, I took them one at a time, and Miri took them one at a time.
Yes, Miri was taking pictures.
Then Mayuka passed by,
And then Shoko came in.
That's right.
Then Sasatsu came, then Keira came, then Ana came, and finally, everyone was having fun together.
Yes, that's right.
That was fun.
Everyone interrupted us, didn't they?
Yes, they really interfered.
I was really taking pictures.
It was kind of cute.
It's good.
It's really good.
Yes, yes, it made me happy. We had a lot of fun.
It was fun.
It's cute.
I want it so much.
I've been getting a lot of requests for this picture.
You know, really.
Oh, I see.
I took a different picture when this music video came out.
Oh, you gave it to them.
You did.
It was after that, right?
Yes, after this.
She's cute.
It's a rare photo.
Yeah.
Okay, then, let's continue. There's more.
Next is a photo that Harisa sent me.Next is a photo sent by Harisa.
Let's take a look. Here you go.
Wow.
He's so cute.
That's a sweetie.
Sweet.
Oh, really?
That's right. You're a spoiled brat.
That's right.
When we were on the Ghibli, Hana-chan was suddenly beside me, and I started to feel sleepy.
I heard it.
That's cute.
Nemu nemu nyan cat.
She was saying "sleepy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy-napy.
It was so cute.
Hana-chan was amazing at this Seven.
Oh, yeah.
I see.
She was so cute.
It was like she was under the spell of Seven.
Me too.
The two of you.
You're under the spell of Seven, aren't you?
This is Japan, you know.
And one more person sent us a picture of flowers.
The next one is from Chiara.
Here it is.
Here you go.
Wow.
Very nice picture.
Great photo.
Very beautiful.
Nice smile.
What's this?
That's Chiara on the boat.
Yes, there was a group of people who wanted to be on the same boat,Yes, there were like people who wanted to be here in the same boat,
We were scared,
Ankoro and Hana-chan didn't want to go.
So, we became a member of the group.
Then they smiled and gave us a peace.
That was amazing.
A very good picture.
But this shot, this scene.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Not the main story.
The last one.
The first photo at the last tuelare.
It takes longer to get here.
At all.
Yes, it does.
I'm glad to see this now.
Nice photo.
It's a bye-bye picture.
Okay, now for the cute pictures section.
The last photo is the one Hitomi sent me.
Here it is.
Here we go.
Don.
Wow, the last one is so cute!
Isn't she cute?
It's pretty much everyone at Lovecreate.
You know, in Love Create.
You know, you were sleeping in your townhouse.
The guy sleeping with his mouth open and the lights on.
It's so funny, I can't help but fly.
It's funny.
It's like he's a dentist.
There's a light above him.There's a light from above.
I can tell I'm a mouth breather when I sleep.
The light is positioned just right.
It's so cute.
sleeping peacefully
Finally, now that we have the perfect picture
I would like to move on to the next theme.
The next one is not limited to this year.
I'd like to talk about the last 6 years
I'd like to talk about the past 6 years.
Then, let's move on.
This way.
I've been keeping it a secret for a long time.
I've been keeping secret.
That's terrible.
Secret? No, it's not.
What did I write?
I asked everyone to fill out a questionnaire.
I'll read it out loud and introduce you.
First of all, let's start with Chiara.
Kiara has been keeping a secret.
about the members
About Maika
I'll make an announcement.
Maika is always trying to eat my fingers.
I'm about to get my fingers eaten.
What do you mean?
I haven't kept it a secret for long.
But...
Fans don't know.
I don't know.
It's always...
Fingers.
It's like it's trying to hold my finger and eat it.He's going to hold it and try to eat it.
I don't understand.
There's a lot of air in here.
There's a lot of air.
Why is he doing that?
I don't know.
Do you have an excuse?
No, I don't.
But I've never eaten anything before.
I'm just trying to eat.
You've never had it?
Do you have a career?
I can't do this anymore.
No, no, no, no.
He really eats.
I'm sure.
He really bites my hands.
And she's pretty stubborn.
She bites.
Do you know what it's like to bite?
I'm not biting.
I'm not biting you.
I'm sorry.
I'm chewing a lot.
I want you to stop.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I don't know what to do.
I want a solution.
The way it's always been.
You'll be doing this for the rest of your life.
And now for the next question.
Mirin answered.
About Hitomi
Hitomi isHitomi...
With a very good posture
Riding a bicycle.
What kind of information?
What's in it for you?
She always has good posture.
He rides a bike.
I don't know much about it.
I was in the dressing room listening to him.
I heard him talking about it
I heard him talking about it.
I wrote it down anyway.
Love Create
I'm good at biking.
I've heard you're good at biking.
I am.
I was a bike tourist.
I was a bike rider, so I had to pedal with great posture.
To pedaling with good posture.
And how fast I can pedal it
and how fast I can pedal gracefully
I was on a long road
I've been doing it for about three years.
I'm really good at riding a bike.
Do you have a project in the works
I'm really
I'm really good at pedaling.
A bike?
I'd love to see you pedal it in front of everyone.
I'll see you on the flower aisle... or on a bicycle.
I'd love to see you do it.
No one's ever let me out.I've never let anyone take me out.
I'll pedal gracefully
Before my heroine
She's not pretty.
What do you think?
Is there anything else you'd like to share with the members that you haven't already shared with them?
Any other stories you've been keeping from the members?
Secrets?
It's a big party, isn't it?
That's right.
What do you talk about?
Anything?
No, right?
We're not secret men and women.
No secret men and women.
That's why I'd like to move on to the last topic.
So many things.
I'm sure there are many.
But due to time constraints, I'd like to introduce just one.
I can say it now.
I'm sorry.
Episode 4.
What, what, what?
What is this? What does it say?
This is Sanna's questionnaire.
May I read it as is?
Six years ago, at a summer camp before my major label debut.
I left some snacks on the table and a bunch of ants came.
Who are these? I pretended I didn't know.
That's me!
Who remembers me?
No, I don't.
You don't remember?
The one where we had two rooms and one of them got ants?
You couldn't sleep?The one where you can't sleep?
Yeah, it's Sana's fault.
Haa!
I remember!
I remember the second night we all slept together.
It was all Sana's fault.
It was summer.
I was pretty nature-rich, wasn't I?
I remember the salad flavor of the candy that you could pop the sugar into.
They're so soft.
I'm going to bed, I'm going to take a bath, I'm going to bed, and then what? There's a black pig.
Oh, my God!
And then it got really intense.
Wow!
And I was like, "Oh no, I'm not going to go to bed.
I went to the living room and slept on a chair in the living room.
Then I saw that someone or something was not moving,
Who is this? I was like, "Who's this? Is he there? Like, "Is that him?
Wow!
That was really amazing.
Oh, really?
We weren't this close then, so I thought he would get mad at me.
If it were now, I could say, "Oh, I'm totally sorry.
I still get angry.
I get angry now.
At that time, everyone was still friendly.
Still. Sure, sure, sure.
I'm really sorry.
That's right.
But I'm glad I don't remember.
I shouldn't have said anything.
If I hadn't told them, they wouldn't have found out, right?
That's for sure.
So, please be good to me. Please do.
Yes, so it was very exciting,Yes, so it has been a very exciting time,
I would like to continue.
Here is the next one.
Let's see what's next.
A great reward, a looting Bomberman.
Looting?
Did you write that?
I don't want to be happy.
I don't want to be a hero.
Reward, nurture, Bomberman showdown!
Yay!
Good!
Excellent.
And now, on to the next part,
With a festive reward,
Let's play Bomberman, with a happy reward.
Now, I'm sure you're wondering what the prize is,
First of all, let me explain the rules.
This time, it is an individual winner-take-all game.
You will face off against three to four other people in each block,
The winning team will play in the final match.
The winner will receive a prize.
What kind of prize?
What? What?
What do you think it is?
Take a guess.
You're going to tell me?
Yes, I will. I'll tell you now.
Not after I teach you?
I'll teach you first,
Here you go.
Eyewitness card!Eye-twister card!
You just want it.
Anything else?
Mr. Cara.
Because the last time something was delivered, it was Disney,
This time it's Universal.
Universal?
That's nice.
It's Christmas time.
The book club.
Would you like to read a book?
Do you read?
Do you want to read?
I read.
You read?
You want to read it?
Read it!
Excellent.
It's hard to get the right answer.
I gave you a hint, didn't I?
What? What? What?
Did you just read that?
What?
Obermann.
What? What?
I'm sorry.
It's an exploding system.
What?
Now.
I can see it! I wanna see it!
I want to! I want to! I want to!
What? TYAKI!
TYAKI!
Colors! Colors!Colors! Colors!
The correct answer is here.
What?
Garming.
Six servings.
For our 6th anniversary,
I'm giving away 6 servings of luxurious Thai shabu-shabu.
I want some of this.
It's so cute!
Is it cute?
So...
How are you doing? Are you okay?
I can't talk.
Thank you, Ty!
Interesting.
But I want to do my best.
Good luck.
Too much pinpointing.
You're the one who should hang in there.
It's a library card that I couldn't find.
I'll do my best!
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, so let's get started.
The first block is,
Hana, Lisa, Chiara, and Iori.
Chiara?
What's that?
Too heavy.
Worst, worst comment,
Alikut character.
Alikut character?
What the hell!
That's terrible!Terrible!
It's not funny.
I thought it was funny. Sorry.
I read your comment.
I don't read them, guys.
This way.
Okay.
Are you ready to stand by? All right, everybody.
Boom, boom.
Okay, let's get you ready.
I mean games, you know, like Kiara.
Games.
No, not a game.
I've done it before.
Like a game.
I'm going to play a game now, so please be careful with your earphones.
Sure thing.
Standard ones are good.
It will damage your ears.
That's true.
So classical music is good?
A lot, indeed.
Well, I'll go with this one.
It's a standard.
Oh, here it comes.
Here it comes.
Just a few rule settings.
Back it up.
Go back.
Just go back.
Here it comes.
You got it?
Oh, it's okay.
Set number two.Sets 2.
Time 2.
OK.
How do you change it?
Oh, just A?
Oh, A. When the avatar comes up.
Oh, here it comes.
Oh, wait, I've made a decision.
I can go back to B.
I'll go with the black book.
It's easy to understand.
It's easier to understand if everyone is different.
What? He's saying something.
It's nice and sparkly.
You wanted to see me.
Is this going to happen?
Why are we fighting?
Yellow.
Why do you fight?
Eh, three.
Look at your color.
Yes, black.
Yellow.
First of all, I think I'm going to be pushed.
Hang in there.
I'm scared.
Ready, go!
What do you want me to do?
Do I just put it here?
Oh, so you're just gonna run away.
Oh, okay.
That's the whole length.
Oh, great, great, great, great.
That's good, that's good, that's good.It's good, it's good, it's good.
What? What's wrong?
It's a close game.
Oh, you're so good.
You're good.
I made a mistake! What's wrong?
Are you kidding me?
Please turn down the volume, everyone.
It's not safe.
What do you want me to do?
This is where it gets dangerous.
No way!
Watch your earphones.
Oh, no!
What's happening?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, shit!
It's official.
I said it first.
Oh, cool!
Who lost?
Stop!
I'm out!
Oh, shit!
We did it!
That's the last one!
If Ciara wins, it's over!
No! Come on, come on, come on!
I can still do it!
Come on, come on, come on!
I think everyone's ears are done here.
I told you first!We said it first!
We are!
We might as well be number one!
Maybe they can hear us without it!
I can't hear you!
What do you want me to do?
What do you want me to...
I don't know,
Would you like to get in line for a little chat alone?
Yes! I'm going upstairs!
Come on!
Watch out!
What's this? What's this round thing? Can I take this one?
This bomber.
You can take it.
What do I get if I take this?
Where is it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, don't come here.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Ahhh...
I've been knocked down
I'm scared.
That's the worst.
It's the worst.
It's the worst!
I want my allowance!
When did this place end, too?
It's coming from up there!
From up there!
Wait!Wait!
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no! When did it end?
What? One more time!
Is there another one?
Not until I get two!
No, no, no!
Come on!
Who's that?
You're getting better!
Hey! Come on, guys!
Come on, come on, come on!
You're getting better!
My mouth is hanging open!
Oh! My mouth is open!
My mouth is open!
I'm opening my mouth with a lie!
Can't you take it off?
What happens if I take it off?
Who took it?
It's crowded!
Did somebody get it?
Oh, my God! It's so dense!
Why is it so dense?
Self-destruct! Self-destruct! Self-destruct!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh no!
I felt terrible.
Oh, no.Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Which one is it?
I'm gonna put it in this one.
I'm gonna stick with this one.
Stop, stop, stop.
Oh, shit.
Ahhh...
Too close, too close
Okay, so...
The winner is
Miyara!
That's what I'm talking about!
That's what I'm talking about.
Is everyone all right?
Are they okay?
It's so frustrating.
Are you okay?
How did it go? I tried it, four of us.
It's frustrating.
Disappointing?
It was a self-destruct, no matter what.
It's hard to do.
I was caught in the middle.
I knew the two of you were strong.
I was able to do it well.
I was good.
It was fun. I did it.
We did it, but it was fun.
Congratulations!
We're here. Chiara.
Yes, I'm here. I love Thailand.
I want to eat some more.
I want to eat Thai.
I won't let you eat it.Don't ever let them eat it.
Yes, I will. Then, let's continue.
Next, Hitomi and Shoko and Minyan. Let's go.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know where Thailand will win.
Hey. How's the game? Are you good at it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. I don't play.
I don't know what's going to happen. I won't do it.
Then, please get ready.
Okay. Please do.
You mean the conveyor.
New ears, please.
New ears.
Come on.
Next, the three of us will face off.
I'll do my best.
Yes, sir.
Decent and rules.
Good night.
4? 4? 4?
Oh, shit.
Is that right?
Where do you want it? Where do you want it?
Anywhere.
Come on!
It's bright.
Oh, my God!
I'm gonna make a boss character.
This one's got flames all around it.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
Red bong, white bong.
Okay! Okay!
Four.
Can't you beat me to the computer?
What are you gonna do?What do you want?
Don't you want a computer?
We can't lose.
Where are you?
Hey, lady.
What's with the fire?
Oh, my God.
It looks like stone.
There's a hill we can climb.
Oh, wow.
Oh, is that what I think it is?
You can climb that hill?
That's what you mean?
If we go this far, we can climb the hill.
What happens if I follow you?
Oh, I got it.
Oh, you're a character.
What do you mean?
I'm scared.
It's so close.
Oh, my God.
What's going on? What?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God. The fight's already started.
Oh, my God. The fight's started? Oh, my God.
Yeah, what does that mean?
Why are we fighting?
Oh, no! I'm scared!
Oh, no.
Oh, shit, he knows.
He's dead.
Oh, no.
Oh, he's down.
He's down.You're beat.
No, we're not done yet.
What, you need a computer? Not yet.
Really, really, really.
Computer's down.
Oh, my God, the computer's down.
Computers are so strong.
I mean, they just keep bringing more and more computers.
What's happening?
Come on! Come on!
Oh, I'm trying!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
I beat the computer, but the computer beat me.
Come on!
Where do I start?
Uh, which way?
Brain cells.
I got it!
I'll have to do it under comments, handsome.
Hit the like button.
Yeah!
The computer got us closer to Thailand!
I really wanted to eat Thai!
I wanted to eat it!
That's good, right!
Throw me a strong computer!
Computer, let's set it a little low!
Weak?
Weak? It's my first time!Are you weak? It's my first time!
It was normal!
Normal!
Now, that's a first!
That was amazing!
One game and now!
You're so weak!
One game!
One set at a time!
Okay!
The easier the better!
That was hard, wasn't it!
Here?
Let's do it here!
Okay! Come on!
I can't lose!
I'm losing!
I called it!
He's strong!
Slow down!
Yes, sir!
Yes!
I want to eat!
I want some!
I want it!
It's a beautiful day!
Come on!
You guys like Thai?
I love Thai!
I want some Thai!
I want to eat Thai!I want to eat!
I want some!
Oh, man! I'm going to get this!
It's starting!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
Oh, my God!
Looks like you've got a story.
Books.
Computer books.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Scary, scary, scary.
The computer's alive.
Computer alive!
Hip!
Yeah! Yeah!
You alone or what?
Come on, man.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Yay!
Congratulations.
What's that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
You want to do it again?
Let's do it again.
It's embarrassing.
Don't stop doing that.
Can I win one more time today?
You're good on the computer.
The computer's only moving a little bit.
There's no wasted time.No wasted motion.
But if the computer wins, it's over.
You're good with computers.
You're good.
Somebody's got to win.
Computer's good.
Let's watch the computer and study it a little bit.
I know how far it'll go before it blows up.
What?
Is it starting?
Oh, shit.
The game's on.
Oh, no.
I don't want you to come.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, he's gone.
He's gone.
Nice.
Get him out of here.
Be careful out there.
There's a fistfight... somebody shove him.
Nice escape.
What? - What? What? What?
What?
What is that?
It says it's gone.
It looks like a piece of candy.
Oh, shit.
There's nothing left.
Oh, my God.
What was that? What did you get?
An item?Item?
What did you do with it?
I was doing something, and then this happened.
That's great.
I was just doing it, and then this happened.
I wonder what happened.
Does that mean he took some kind of item?
Some kind of item.
I picked up something.
That's great.
So...
The winner is Hitomi.
That's great!
You did it!
Amazing!
I don't know what it is anymore, but...
Oh, it's a machine.
Amazing.
It's amazing.
You have it.
I have it.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Good job.
Now, the last three are Maika, Sano, and me.
Okay.
What? Like Angel and Gretel from earlier.
Definitely.
Angel and Gretel.
That was amazing.
What? What's going on? Now.
It's really Idol and Gretel.
They're all over the place somewhere.
But it's amazing.But it's great.
I might let you do it yourself.
I might even let you do it yourself.
So you were able to do it without knowing anyone.
It's so funny.
It's funny, isn't it?
Bomber Namer.
What are these?
Battle rules?
Is this a Japanese player?
Yes.
Japanese player.
What do you like?
You want to fight?
You want to fight in the corner.
Where do you want it?
Hmmm.
I like the shoulder.
Okay, I'll put it here.
Okay.
White. White bon.
What color would be easier to recognize? Like this one?
She's cute.
Okay, let's go with green.
Okay.
It's a great red. It's on fire.
Oh, man. I won't lose, I promise.
Go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go! Which one am I?
Wait, which one is me?
Which one's Sanla? Lower right.
Lower right? Red.
What? Where am I going?
What is it? It's stuck.
What? Which one's Sanla?
Red, yellow, top right.Red, yellow, top right.
I was looking at the wrong one.
They keep running like that.
They kept running like that.
They just keep going.
They can't stop.
They just keep running like that.
I'm meeting people.
They're meeting.
Oh no, they're all here.
Oh, no.
We beat them.
I got him.
It flew.
Combination.
Nice.
Aaaaah!
Oh no!
Maybe we can pull here?
Oh, no. Maybe we can attack from the outside.
From the outside? Okay, okay.
Don't attack from the outside!
It's too fast.
Aaah!
You did it!
I don't know what's going on, but...
Same! Same!
Which one?
The bottom right.
It's Thai.
I want some Thai.
Thai, Thai, Thai.
You know what I'm saying?
Do you want a skull?
You can take it.You can take it.
Dokuro, what is it?
It's moving so slow.
It's slow like that.
There's a skull.
Can I take the skull?
I would never take a skull.
Don't lie to me!
Who is it? The guy who just said it's okay to take it.
You're moving too slow.
You're fast!
He's fast.
Look out! Look out!
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Get out! Come on, get out! Get out of that narrow space!
Oh no...
Aahhh!
Aaaaahhh!
Aah! I'm scared!
Computer.
Computers never lose.
Oh, well, me too.
I'm good over here.
I'm over here.
I'll go this way.
The computer's stronger.
I'll take this one.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Ahhh...
Hey, computer!
Oh, shit!
This is crazy!
Somebody's doing it!Somebody's doing it!
Hey, computer!
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait! I'll let myself in!
Whoo-hoo!
You mean you're gonna let the guy in from the inside?
Yeah, I'm gonna let the man in from the outside.
Let's have a foursome!
Make it a 4-way!
Four-way is gone!
That's gone! That's it!
What? What? Huh? What?
That's my car!
Hey!
You're wasting your time!
Stop it!
Stop!
Wait!
Come back! Come back!
Aah!
That's my car!
What? What?
Stop it! Stop it!
Come on, Anzu! Come on, Anne! Come on, girl!
Come on, An-no-hang on! Hold on, An! Go, Anne!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
Which one is the computer face?
There, there, there!
Bottom left!
You've been after me this whole time!
What? Why?
The black one!The black one!
The black one!
Where is he?
It's right in front of me!
I'm scared!
I'm afraid of the dark!
Where should I run to?
I'll never get out.
Where do I run to?
This way!
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
Scary!
Hey!
That's scary!
That's the color! That color!
This girl!
Everybody, hit me!
That sparkly!
Pinko Pewter.
That's you!
Computer.
It's Rust!
Which one?
Wait!
I just wanna check the yawp first!
I'm gonna have to ask you to turn left.
Left?
Down left.
Same one?
Same one.
White bonnet.
Keep it.
You're scaring me!You're scaring me!
Do it again!
It's more than Anpanman.
He's coming this way.
Hey!
I'm stopping you right there.
That one, right there.
There... there... there...
There it is.
OK, OK.
OK, let's go for it.
I'm already scared.
It's like...
Like a tutor.
I'm scared.
I'm not scared yet.
Are you enjoying this?
Are you having fun?
Are they laughing their asses off?
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Wow! Nice, nice!
There's smoke, smoke, smoke!
Oh, there's smoke, smoke, smoke!
Oh, isn't that scary?
Oh, I can smell it!
Oh, it's burning!
Shut up, it's burning!
It's on fire!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Wait, why, why?
Shut up!
Whoa!
No!
Not yet!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
Where?
There!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Did you get it?
I don't know if I won.
You don't know if you won.
That was a great tiebreaker.
Did I win once?
You won once?
Congratulations.
Good luck.
Except for Chiara, these two,
I mean, they don't even know what they're doing.
Good luck.
They don't seem to be scared.
I'll do my best.
Hang in there.
You're doing great.
You're trembling.
I'm sorry I said so much.
Thank you.
Okay, the three of us for the last time,
Makeup store.
Good luck.
I'm rooting for all three of you.
There are some people who shouldn't be here, but they are,
Help us.
You don't know what's going on.
I'm rooting for you. I really am.
Hang in there.Go for it.
You'll be surprised, I'm sure.
But help me.
Why did you think I wouldn't make a fuss?
It's me, isn't it?
Good luck.
It was fun.
Yes, it was.
Okay, let's have a verification battle.
What are the battle rules?
Computerized.
What do we do? At the last makeup store.
Let's try the last one.
No, no, no, no.
No.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay. Whatever.
Stable.
Like this, like this.
It's good.
They're in the finals, so I guess...
The op-ed writer.
It's true.
Level 5.
A little bit of an oputer.
I'm a little bit of an op-uter.
He's been winning, so he's been relatively...
It's stable.
All right.
Let's go.
Let's take down the oputer.
First, let's take out the oputer.
Second step.2nd step.
OK.
I'll take care of it.
White.
It's white.
I'm scared.
Suddenly white.
All right.
I'm nervous.
White. Leftmost.
Okay.
Good luck.
You can only beat the computer.
You can't lose.
I don't care who wins.
Only if we don't lose to the computer.
You can't lose.
It's true.
We're getting closer to the computer.
That's good.
I'm on the attack.
Computer.
Yay.
Nice.
Album.
Oh no.
Let me do it.
Oh no, I'm fucked.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.Oh, no.
He's doing it from so far away.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This guy's really freaking me out.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Help me!
Oh, my God! Watch out!
You'll get buried from the outside.
Oh, my God!
Which way? Which way?
Keeno's the panna.
Come on.
Ahhh...
Keeno is the panna.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
That's so cool.
One more?
Twice!
I have to do two.
And because of the time.
Oh, God.
He's always around.
Mr. Yoshimoto.
Maybe there's a ket...
Hey, there might be
I fell down.
Aaaaah! He's gone.
Aaaaah!
Is there a ket?
He's gone.
There it is!There it is!
Oh, no.
It's from outside.
Ahhh...
Then knock him down!
What the hell was that? Data from here!
Zion key.
Computer, you're good.
Computer, don't say "computer"...
Computer, you're good. Aim at the computer.
I'm not good at it...
Neroyaki
I'm sorry, guys.
Oh, no.
But I'm not done.
Not yet.
Japanese practice.
That's right.
Still kindergarten.
Next, for example.
This guy can't be bothered.
I'm gonna go take him down from the computer.
Yeah, right.
Absolutely.
Once the computer does.
I hope he gets mad.
Computer.
Right here at the computer.
You want me to go to the computer?
I'm gonna go now.
I'll be careful going around the block.
This is...
I hope we go to the computer.
Iris!
Okay!
Okay!Ok!
Yeah!
Please.
Piano.
He's still alive.
Whoa! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Whoa! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Whoa!
You can do it. You can do it. Come on! Nice try!
You! Pinch, pinch!
You!
You! Wait!
Wait! What's going on?
Come on, Chiara!
Come on! Chiara!
Wait a minute! Kiara!
Come on, Kiara!
I don't want to lose to Kiara!
Go, Kiara!
You can do it!
I can do it!
Go, Kiara!
You can do it!
What do I do? What do I do?
Come on, Chiara!
Wow!
Nice! Nice!
Ah!
Wow!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh no!Oh no! Oh no! Oh, no!
Are you coming in there?
Is that where you're coming? Like that?
What do we do?
I can do it!
Whoo!
That's good.
Help!
Aahhh!
Aaaaah!
I'm in the middle of all kinds of training.
Wait!
Strong!
Thank you!
He wants to do it again!
Is this it?
Then let's make it last!
Let's make it last!
Good luck!
We're gonna beat the computer!
That's right!
Let's beat the computer first!
Once!
Why can't we beat it!
Really!
Can you do it in one go?
Can you beat it in one go?
We're doing it with three people!
I know you can do it!
It's a computer, it's smart!
It's so strong!
Are you having a good time?
Come on, computer.Comeon Computer
I have a sore throat.
I know what you mean.
It's like watching a sports game.
I can't do it with just the three of us.
Here.
Uh...
I'm doing it.
Hang in there.
All right.
Come on.
The computer.
First things first.
If everyone fails...
Yuka.
Your mouth...
Your face is crooked.
Don't worry, it's fine. You're doing great.
You look worried.
It's the computer.
I'm attacking the computer.
I can't get at the computer.
It's coming from outside, outside, outside.
I can't get a clear shot.
I won't allow it, I won't allow it, I won't allow it.
How did it get through?
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Cu-cu-cu.
Nice!
A final worthy of a final. Finally.
Finally.Finally.
Oh, the computer's gone. I'll be outside, so watch out computer.
Oh, but soon.
Oh, it's gone.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
It's gone. See, we can bury them from the outside.
Oh, Chiara and Hitami.
Oh, no, they're digging outside.
Be careful.
It's Chiara and Hitami.
Oh, no, hang in there.
Hang in there.
Oh!
Chiara is running away.
So, the winner is Kiara!
Congratulations!
What do you think?
How do you feel? How does it feel to win now?
I feel very happy!
It's great!
Congratulations!
Oh my God, is everyone's throat okay?
Oh no! Oh no!
Of course my throat is bad, and everyone's ears are bad. No doubt about it.
But I remember it was super fun.
It was fun.
I wish I could have done it. I wanted to do this.
I wanted to do it.
I'm glad.
So, that's all for now, everyone.
Bom-bom-bom-bom.
I'm tired. My throat.
So, let's move on to the next project.
Hana-chan, please.
Equal Love Grand Strategy Meeting.Equal Love Grand Strategy Meeting.
This is finally the seventh year of Equal Love,
We would like to have a strategy meeting to make this year's activities more fulfilling.
In advance, we would like to ask fans what they would like Equalab to do from now on,
And one more thing is the goods we want Equal Love to make.
Legs.
I want you to make legs.
We have conducted a survey on the two goods that we would like Equalab to make.
I would like to talk about the results of the survey in a ranking format.
We have received about 2,000 responses to our survey.
Thank you very much.
Let's start with the ranking.
First, let's start with the No. 5 ranking of what we want Equalabs to do.
Here it is.
Makeup project.
I want you to do one makeup game. I'm very interested in makeup, so I want to see what each member's makeup looks like.
And they want to exchange makeup pouches and do makeup.
What do you think? How do you like it?
Each of you is different.
The points of particularity are different, too.
You can count on this.
Maybe it will be a comingsoon.
That's comingsoon, isn't it?
Please look forward to it.
Next is No. 4.
This is No. 4. This way.
Cooking project.
A member who is good at cooking instructs a member who is not good at cooking to cook a dish.
I want them to challenge themselves to cook without looking at any recipes.
And Shoko's cooking class.
What do you think, Shoko?
I've been wanting to do this for a long time, but it's been difficult because I've tried so many things on my own.
But I think it's time to do it.
I want you to do it.
I want to have fun with everyone.
What would you do if you had to divide up the members who are good at it and those who are not?What would you do if you had to divide the members who are good at something into those who are not good at it?
Not good at it.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm definitely good at it, mom.
Not absolutely.
I'm absolutely good at it.
You must be a bad member.
I'm not good at it.
Three people, Type B trio.
Type B trio.
I hope we can do it together someday.
I want to do it.
I'd like to make it with just the three of us, without any instructions.
Sounds great!
That's a good idea.
We could come up with a very difficult theme.
Like Chikuzen.
Chikuzen isn't too difficult.
Wasn't it meat?
Let's do it like this.
That's for sure.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please move it.
Let's do it sometime.
Then here is the third place.
I tried singing.
I would like to see various pairs of collaborators singing together.
The video I tried singing of Ikaring.
When singing in kindergarten.
What do you mean?
I want you to sing.
Bloom, bloom, tulip flowers.
Darandarandarandaran.
Red, white and yellow.
Yes, I sang.Yes, I sang.
I think this is also what you just wrote.
Thanks.
Easy.
What do you think?
I often sing, like in a chorus.
Isn't that it? We sang that at Sebutou, didn't we?
We all sang at Sebutou too.
Twinkle, Twinkle, Twinkle Stars.
In loungewear.
Oh, I heard it.
I heard it.
That's good. That's good.
I want to say it.
Yes, by all means, everyone sleep in it now.
Uh-huh.
Okay, here's the second place.
Karaoke.
Karaoke?
Why?
Suddenly?
I'm going home with you.
I'll go home with you.
I'll go home with you, and maybe we'll do karaoke.
Karaoke, maybe next Thanksgiving.
Sure.
I'll do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I don't know, I've never done it before.
Everyone is really confused.
That's for sure.Certainly.
Yeah.
Yes, that's for sure.
But there seems to be a divide between the songs you know and the ones you don't know.
That's right.
Last time we played here, there was a time when we wanted to play Disney tickets,
I'm sure.
But, you know, that was too much fun, wasn't it?
Over 80 points for a song I don't know.
Ah.
For sure.
Indeed.
While watching it in the film.
Certainly.
Someday.
It looks difficult.
Then, you're in first place, aren't you?
Here you go.
Here is the first place.
Uh...
Uh.
Eh. I want to do it. Yeah, I've never done it.
I've never done it.
Yeah, I've never done it before.
But, you know, Hana-chan made a mistake earlier,
Huh?
Right.
I didn't make a mistake.
That kind of thing comes out.
It's true that everyone seems to be weak.
I want to do it.
I'm sure you can do it.
You're kidding?
So, let's keep who's a total ass. This is...So let's seal who's a goofball. This is.
They know.
No, you don't.
No, no, no, no. I'm not.
I'm absolutely fine with it, but I'm not doing it for everyone.
For everyone's sake.
But we're gonna be okay.
Yeah, we're fine. Totally.
No, no, no, no. For everyone's honor.
I don't want to damage their honor. As a leader.
I see. I understand.
I understand.
We'll discuss the sealing.
We'll discuss the sealing. Let's discuss it with the adults.
Someday we'll have fun.
Yes.
Yes. That's why, though,
Next, let me ask you something,
I have received the same questionnaire from everyone else,
I would like to introduce them to you.
First of all, Miryan.
Miryan. I want to do pottery.
I want to do pottery.
Is there anyone who wants to do ceramics?
Yes, I do.
I'm glad to hear that.
You know, you can do pottery like this,
I can paint it and make my own tableware.
It's great.
It's fun.
I want to do it with a specific video or something.
I want to do it. I want to do it.
Original.
I like it.Great.
I can cook from there.
Sure.
Might be good.
It might be good.
Come on, let's go one more.
Next, we have Sana.
Sana is for a surprise show,
I'd love to have her on the show as a surprise act.
That's right. I'm a trickster.
It says that I'm a gimmicky person,
Please let me hook you.
What kind of surprises do you have in mind?
Ghosts, for example.
Oh no.
It's scary, isn't it?
They've been doing this to me all day.
A big accident. Big accident.
I want to do it.
It sounds like fun.
Let me do it. It's about time.
Surprise me.
It's a good reaction.
It's worth it. For Sanna.
Let's see what kind of project you guys come up with,
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of project will be adopted.
Now, let's move on to another theme.
What kind of goods do you want Equalab to make?
Let's make this one lucky, too.
Here is the fifth place.
Accessories.
I want some amazing clothes for the members of Equalab.
Oshiyuwa.
Eh, what's that?
Stand oshikari.
Eh, what's that?Eh, what's that?
A fashionable accessory that I can use on a daily basis since I am a student.
Cute.
It's nice.
Sure is.
I might have paired it with a variety of earrings.
Sure.
That's nice.
Cute. Definitely.
Men, please wear them, too.
I'll wear both.
You can wear it either way.
By all means.
Now, and here is the fourth place.
Sticker.
It's a sticker that appeared in Heroines.
Nice.
A sticker you can put on your phone.
It's really nice, isn't it?
It's a sticker with illustrations of the members.
I want one.
You can have as many stickers as you want.
I want to put them on my phone.
Yes, indeed.
There is demand.
The Heroines stickers.
That one. This one?
It's cute, isn't it?
This one. I want you to make a lot of them.
I'm sure.
They all fit each other.
It's good. Thank you very much.No problem. Thank you.
You have good taste.
And here is the third place.
I guess this is it.
Libs. Heh.
I want Ikola's ribs. Ribs by far. I want ribs in member colors, even if they are flashy.
Member-colored libs. Like yellow.
I'm going to be a Yatsuchan.
I guess this is something we need to discuss. Yes, that's right.
There are people who make them for everyone. Ikora is wearing black now, you know.
It's because they are libs. That's right. It's all black.
But there are also key chains and such, aren't there? Oh, yes, key chains.
Please wear it. Please wear it.
And here comes the second place.
Oh, a smartphone game.
I want it. I might want it.
Oh, then you can make a VIVS phone case.
What do you mean?
Combine them?
A black VIVS phone case with the member's name Hitomi Takamatsu.
A black phone case.
We'll combine them, won't we?
Match them up.
What do you think? What do you think of the comment section?
VIVS is fine.
Phone case. I definitely want one.
But what kind of phone case?
I'm not sure if it's pink or something, but it's hard to use.
And if you're going to put stickers on it, fly behind it.
It's definitely nice.
I'll put it right here on the side of the phone.
Maybe it could be synchronized.
I thought clear would be good.
Then you can put it between the stickers.
Like a charm, like a charm designed by the members.
Cute.It's cute.
I can wear it.
Like VIVS.
VIVS is nice.
Oh?
That's for sure.
That's right.
It's very practical.
Phone case.
It's nice that you can take it to work and not look like a dork.
That's for sure.
Casually.
It's a way to show off casually.
It's nice.
A phone case I want.
That's a good candidate for a phone case.
Now, then, ladies and gentlemen, the first place.
Huh? What is it?
Here is the second place.
Oh!
I want it! I want it!
Now, I want you to make a Chibifi of the members. I want a plushie that I can carry around.
I want to make Chibifi and so on.
I want it! I want it!
I'll make costumes and stuff.
If we make them and change their clothes, they'll be even cuter.
About 4 of the members said that they want to make an Equal Love character.
Yes, I want an Equal Love character.
It would be cute, for sure.
It's true.
I want to make one. And you took our picture in the photo album.
Yes, that's right.
It's cute.
I see.
So cute!
They are cute, aren't they?It's cute.
And the fan holding it is cute too.
So cute!
I want one!
And, you know, characters are kind of casual, so they can be worn a lot.
That's true. Students also wear them on their bags.
That's cute.
That would broaden the range of goods.
Since this is the number one item on the list, let's consider it.
Please, staff, please.
Please do.
Now then, what kind of goods would each member like to have?
Yes, I wrote "stuffed animals" in my wish list.
I was so happy that I didn't think I won the first place.
I quit!
I want to make one someday.
Let's make it.
How about you, Shioko?
The feather pin I used to do in gaming is a collaborative feather pin.
Eh, I like it!
I want to make a lucci art, like the cinnamon one they're doing right now, because that's cute.
I want one!
I want it!
I want that, too, when they make a character, when they make a character.
Oh, it's super cute!
It's so good!
It will definitely sell.
Even feather pins are sold no matter how many there are.
That's for sure.
We use them every day.
That's great.
Please look forward to seeing what kind of goods we will be able to produce in the future.
Yes!
Yes! Now that we've had our fun, is it time to move on to the next section?
Yes, of course!Eh, of course!
Yes, so that's the last one, this way.
Hana-chan, please.
More excitement for the 6th anniversary! Ikolobu Announcement Corner!
Yay!
Now, here we are, for the Equal Love 6th Anniversary Premium Concert on October 18th and 19th, and we're going to have a lot of fun.
We have prepared 4 contents for the fans to enjoy.
We would like to introduce them to you. Here is the first one!
Instagram Music Stamps of all songs released in the past!
Music stamps of all songs are now available on Instagram. Wallpapers will also be available on social networking sites. Please use it!
I'm so happy. Some of our fans used the stamps right away.
I think they did.
I think they did. The members were using it too.
Please use it a lot and spread the word about Equalove-chan. Please spread the word.
Now, here is the second one.
Equal Love 5th Anniversary Premium Concert and Nationwide Tour 2022
The sound data from the LINE CUBE Shibuya concert will be distributed through various download streaming services.
It was the 5th anniversary a year ago. It's the 5th anniversary of LINE CUBE Shibuya concert a year ago, and it's going to be made into a sound recording.
It's amazing.
That's great. You can listen to it as much as you want.
Please listen to it as much as you can.
Please do.
Well, it's not over yet.
Next up!
Ta-da!
The live video will be distributed through various download streaming services!
Oh my God!
Amazing!
It's amazing, isn't it?
From the concert.
I'm embarrassed that it's the first time!
Isn't it amazing?
It's so nostalgic.
All this.
You mean you get to see it through experience.
It's amazing.It's amazing.
That's awesome.
I'm looking forward to our 6th anniversary.
I'm sure you'll grow up a little bit.
Let's look at it every day.
I'd be happy if everyone could look back and give us a history.
Please do so.
And now....
I'd like to discuss this with you.
The videos up to the 4th anniversary are streaming.
I would like fans to see the 5th anniversary video as well, wouldn't you?
Yes, that's right.
That's why,
Equal Love 5th Anniversary Premium Concert and
National Tour 2022 No matter how you think about it, you love Equal Love!
from the LINE CUBE Shibuya concert.
Two songs from each
I will distribute the video on Equal Love's official YouTube
and which songs will be distributed.
And we are discussing which songs to distribute with our fans right now.
Let's decide together now.
Let's take a look at the setlist. Welcome to the setlist.
It's difficult.
I think it would be good if we don't have the live videos that have been shown in the past. It's better to see various songs.
I want to see Aika's mistake.
What? That's the 4th anniversary. Does that mean it will be released?
I love that one.
That's going to be shown to the public.
I see.
I love it so much.
I love it the most. I'm imitating him all the time.
Ai-chan.
I get a lot of comments.
What do you get a lot of?
BSL, for example.
I guess it's the fan's choice.I knew it was a fan's choice.
So you will start with "Yoyogi"?
Yes.
The best 5th anniversary song.
As for Yoyogi, the fairy's costume was really cute, so I would like to include one of her songs.
Yes, for sure.
Fairy.
That's a good idea.
Why?
Where did it start?
The second half?
Sluggish?
Is it a sizzle? I remember.
Where did it go from "sizzling" to "sizzling"?
There were subliminals.
What? I don't remember that.
What's going on here?
I don't know.
What's the order of "Zuruzuru"?
Zuruzuru ano ko dai darin, dai lilin, aikatsu, natsumatsuri, subliminal.
What?
What? So you came to the end?
The second half, Rescue, is it last?
The end. The end of the film.
You mean you were there?
Like the festival.
Which one are you choosing now?
The 5th anniversary.
The Joyotai.
I'm so confused.
Melanesian is so full of them.
There is a way to have the comment section be only for the 5th anniversary songs.
Let's start from the 5th anniversary and decide.
Everyone wants to see different songs.
Yes, they are. It's pretty spread out.
That girl is a good cell.That's a good cell.
Nice cell.
Is it all broken up?
Hmm.
She has a lot of pins and needles, too.
Yes, she does.
Hey, do we have any pincelfish yet?
In the video.
I don't think so.
I don't think there are any in Daimyojo.
Was this the first time it was shown here?
Hmmm...
It's a line from the top of Yamadai.
Yes, that's right.
It was like a bang.
And it was the first song, right?
That's right.
You have beautiful bangs.
It's important.
Yes, it is.
It might be.
Maybe it's a pincer.
Pinchel?
We've decided on a song.
Pincel.
Pinsel.
The second song.
The beginning was cool.
Yeah, it was cool.
It was cool, wasn't it?
I wonder what's good about it.
I'm happy with anything.
Let's go to a summer festival.
I liked it.
Yes, you did.Right.
Hagoromo costume.
Feather garment.
Fairies.
Where was I with the fairies?
From cheating to smiling lessons.
From sizzle to ?
To the recipe for a smile.
Is she cute?
Cute.
It's cute.
Zulu Zulu that girl.
Great darling, great Lily love and summer festival subliminal.
Eh...
It's difficult.
Big darling subliminal.
Big Lily Love and.
It's difficult.
Is there any song in that fairy costume that you haven't mentioned yet?
Substitute... Substitute Summer Festival Aikatsu...
I don't know. I guess there are a lot of them. I'm lost.
I'm lost. What do you think of the comment section? Too many? Too many? A little bit on hold?
Hold off a bit? No, I'm good. Just for a while!
Line. She likes you, right? You like the club?
You like the club? What about this one? Two songs.
Let's decide. What was I wearing? Hey, gal.
Oh! Here it comes! Gal! You like gal! Gal! That outfit is so cute! I like the gal outfit.
I love it! That outfit gal! Did you turn it off?
I think it was just up to the color pink? Pink? Oh! And there's the root line!
What's that? Poison? I thought we had a root canal? Hair? I think it was Poison. With the blessing.
Right? I think it was a root streak! I'm so embarrassed I did the festival with my gal's earrings on!
I feel like I'm winning. What is it?
BPM will speed up.BPM will be faster.
What do you need? More festivals and poison? That's good! That's good!
Poison? Ah! It's back!
Do the poses! Gal, do Poison!
Poison! She came down before the chorus and I was like... I miss it!
I miss it!
Was that her first Mai Mai or her first performance?
It was her first time! Was it? Was that the first time she showed off her outfit? Yes, she did!
I like Poison! I want to see Poison! I want to see Poison!
Then let's do Poison! Poison!
Another song? So many festivals! There's so many festivals!
Let's do Festival! There's a question left!
Let's get the one with the right earrings!
You want her? Or that one! The festival only comes in this year!
Which one did you wear for your unveiling, Hannah? I don't know! Maybe a different place?
Let's play it!
So let's cut the festivities for now!
Shall we go with "Festival"? Let's make it a festival!
I love festivals! What? What do you think?
But if it's a festival, I'm sure Hannah will be cool with it!
Don't worry! I'm fine with just one earring!
It's cool even if it's attached! It's cute with it!
The cute factor is here!
It'll be cool to see this cute Hannah doing something cool!
It's gonna be so cool! Want to see it? The festival!
I want to see it! Please! Come on, people, it's already a festival!
If you like what I see!
Let's do it! Let's do it!
Kakkari!
Kick Poison and make it a festival!
One more! One more! Yo-tan!
What do we do, Yotan?
A nice selphish and...
I like the fairy outfit!
I'm okay with this one too!
What shall we do?what to do?
be worried
Aoi.
There are a lot of girls.
So many anakos.
Lily has a lot, too.
Lily too
Not Ega, Ega, Ega Shippi.
Egashippi?
Egashipi.
Not this one...
It's "egashippi".
It's our 5th anniversary.
What's this?
Oh, but I guess he remembered it's the 5th anniversary.
A feather here?
A feather here, too.
So it's a clap.
It's hard.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Maybe there's too many dairi. Dairi and that girl.
His getting ready?
I don't know, she didn't walk.
Maybe he did.
Oh, stop?
Wait, we'll never make it in time.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Let's just say we're going that way too.
That's good, right?
It's good.
Okay?
It's good, right?
How's it going?
It's more than cool, isn't it?
Yeah, I think so.Indeed.
Poison, Celebration, and B-Selfish
What do you think?
I think it's good.
Kakari's in it, too.
That's right.
Let's go with B-Selfish and That Girl Complex.
We've decided on four songs.
But there's a possibility it could change.
That's for sure.
Certainly.
Let's leave it at "sure".
Summarize?
Can I ask you to summarize it better?
Summarized.
Yes, please.
The 5th anniversary one is B-Selfish and Anko Complex.
And for the tour, Equal Love Suki...
Poison and Celebration. Cool.
Cool.
I'm looking forward to it.
Looking forward to it!
And here's the fourth and final announcement!
What?
On the official YouTube channel of B-SELFISH
the making of the music video!
What about?
What of what?
What is it?
There's a lot of people who haven't seen it, right?
That's right.
That's for sure.
Now, everyone, let's wait and see which making of will be shown to the public.
Please look forward to it!Please look forward to it!
Please do!
And that's all for the announcement for the 6th anniversary concert!
Yes...
We've made a lot of announcements, so let's get them out of the way.
First of all, we will be distributing all songs on Instagram and music stamps!
And the 5th year concert soundtrack!
5th year or 5th anniversary?
Streaming of the 5th anniversary concert music will also be available.
And streaming of concert videos from the 1st to 4th anniversaries
And the concert video of the 5th year will be available on YouTube.
And the making of the concert will be shown on YouTube.
So there were a lot of things!
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much!
It's great! It's so exciting!
It's too much!
So, there have been a lot of announcements, but it's almost time to say goodbye,
I'm going to say bye-bye now, but...,
But I have one more important announcement to make.
Now, please take my car.
We, Equal Love, are going to release our 15th single.
November 29th, the day of meat!
We will all do our best to make it another good song, so please look forward to it.
It's a celebration with everyone's meat ka.
Let's eat meat together.
Yes, so how was everyone's delivery today? Member.
It was fun.
What time is it? Now.
16:00.
It's been more than an hour, so thank you all very much for your time.
And please continue to support Equal Love in its seventh year.
That's all for now.
Bye bye.Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to our channel.
[Please subscribe to our channel.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
Hm...
Hm
mmm